ipinfodb.com 2019-11-26

# Privacy Policy | IPInfoDB

Thank you for visiting IPInfoDB’s Privacy Policy which relates to data collected for use in our products and services. Our full Privacy Policy below which should help you understand IPInfoDB and how we use the data. 

#### Scope

We respect the right of individuals to privacy. Our Privacy Policy explains: 

  * Who we are
  * What kinds of personal data we may hold about you
  * How we obtain data about you
  * Cookies and other tracking technology
  * What we do with personal data
  * Who we may share your personal data with
  * Data retention and transfers
  * Security
  * Your rights
  * Age limitations
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Limitation of liability

#### Who we are

IPInfoDB is operated by Hexasoft Development Sdn. Bhd. and is located in Pulau Pinang, Malaysia. Individuals wishing to contact us about data protection issues may do so by emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### What kinds of personal data we may hold about you

IPInfoDB may collect and hold personal data such as names, addresses, emails, telephone numbers, IP addresses and cookies. This information may be kept in its identifiable form, or in an aggregated form (so that individuals cannot be identified), for the purposes listed below. The site does not allow third parties to collect personally identifiable information about you related to your online activities when you use this site. 

#### How we obtain data about you

For our website users, we will require information like email address for the purpose of account creation to access services on our website. 

#### Cookies and other tracking technology

A cookie is a small data file that certain Websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. IPInfoDB Website use cookies to track user traffic. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. 

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of IPInfoDB Website & Web Service if you do so. 

#### What we do with personal data

For our website users, the personal data will be used to fulfil your requests for certain products and services, to personalize your experience on our Website, to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, service updates, special offers or other information we think you'd like to hear about either from us or from our business partners, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. We may also use your information to send you, or to have our business partners send you, direct marketing information or contact you for market research. 

#### Who we may share your personal data with

This section describes how IPInfoDB may share and disclose Information. 

  * **Customer’s Instructions.** We will solely share and disclose personal data in accordance with a customer’s instructions, including any applicable terms in the Customer Agreement and Customer’s use of Services functionality, and in compliance with applicable law and legal process.
  * **Third Party Service Providers and Partners.** We may engage third party companies or individuals as service providers or business partners to process Other Information and support our business. These third parties may, for example, provide virtual computing and storage services.
  * **Corporate Affiliates.** IPInfoDB may share Other Information with its corporate affiliates, parents and/or subsidiaries.
  * **During a Change to IPInfoDB Business.** If IPInfoDB engages in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, sale of some or all of IPInfoDB’s assets or stock, financing, public offering of securities, acquisition of all or a portion of our business, a similar transaction or proceeding, or steps in contemplation of such activities (e.g. due diligence), some or all personal information may be shared or transferred, subject to standard confidentiality arrangements.
  * **Aggregated or De-identified Data.** We may disclose or use aggregated or de-identified personal information for any purpose. For example, we may share aggregated or de-identified information with prospects or partners for business or research purposes.
  * **To Comply with Laws.** If we receive a request for information, we may disclose personal information if we reasonably believe disclosure is in accordance with or required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process.
  * **To enforce our rights, prevent fraud, and for safety.** To protect and defend the rights, property or safety of IPInfoDB or third parties, including enforcing contracts or policies, or in connection with investigating and preventing fraud or security issues.
  * **With Consent.** IPInfoDB may share personal information with third parties when we have consent to do so.

#### Data retention and transfers

We will hold the minimum amount of personal data from our website users for communications and allowing access to our services. 

The deletion of personal data may result in the deletion and/or de-identification of certain features. 

#### Security

We have gone to great lengths to secure our server infrastructure to protect the data as best as we can. These steps take into account the sensitivity of the Other Information we collect, process and store, and the current state of technology. 

Given the nature of communications and information processing technology, IPInfoDB cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others. 

  * **Data and System Security:** The personal data contained within our data center is protected by multiple layers and techniques that conform to security industry standards and guidelines.
  * **Security Audit:** IPInfoDB performs security audits and scans on our system on a regular basis to check for vulnerabilities.

#### Your rights

Individuals may request access to, deletion or correction of their personal data, or restrict or object to the use of their data by emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Age limitations

To the extent prohibited by applicable law, IPInfoDB does not allow use of our services and websites by anyone younger than 18 years old. If you learn that anyone younger than 18 has unlawfully provided us with personal data, please contact us and we will take steps to delete such information. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

IPInfoDB may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Laws, regulations and industry standards evolve, which may make those changes necessary, or we may make changes to our business. We will post the changes to this page and encourage you to review our Privacy Policy to stay informed. 

If we make changes that materially alter your privacy rights, IPInfoDB will provide additional notice, such as via email or through the web site. If you disagree with the changes to this Privacy Policy, you should deactivate your account. 

#### Limitation of liability

UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL IPINFODB BE LIABLE TO THE USERS OR ANY OTHER THIRD PARTY FOR ANY INDIRECT, DIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY CHARACTER ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE PRODUCT OR SERVICES PROVIDED UNDER THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR THE BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR RELATING TO ANY OTHER SUBJECT MATTER OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IPINFODB'S LIABILITY FOR ALL CLAIMS ARISING OUT OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT ACTUALLY RECEIVED BY IPINFODB IN CONNECTION WITH THE PROVISION OF IPINFODB SERVICES UNDER THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND USERS AGREE THAT THE FOREGOING SHALL CONSTITUTE USERS'S EXCLUSIVE REMEDY. THE USERS HEREBY RELEASES IPINFODB, ITS OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES AND AFFILIATES FROM ANY AND ALL OBLIGATIONS, LIABILITIES AND CLAIMS IN EXCESS OF THIS LIMITATION. 

Effective date: 24th April 2018
